codeswholesale.com 2015-05-15

# codeswholesale.com

#### Statement of Privacy

Welcome to CodesWholesale.com website. As your comfort is our priority, we respect each visitor's right to personal privacy. We are committed to maintaining the privacy and security of the personal information of all the visitors of this website. We want our users to always be aware of any information we collect, how we use and protect it from being disclosed to others, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website.

#### Collection of Personal Information

You can visit CodesWholesale.com website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, certain pages on our website request personal information from you i.e. if you register to our system, use our API, request information about our products or make an order. The requested information typically includes contact details such as name, address, telephone number and e-mail address. Revealing personal information is completely voluntary, and the user therefore has the choice whether or not to disclose this information. The information we collect are used for: fulfilling requests, improving the content of our website, notifying visitors about updates of our website/products, and are never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we believe such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our web site. In addition, CodesWholesale.com may disclose personal information if it believes such action is required to protect the personal safety of users of CodesWholesale.com, its websites or the public.

#### Log Files

We use log files just like most standard website servers. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service providers (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform types, date/time stamps, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

#### Cookies

CodesWholesale.com uses cookies on our website that are required for the operation of website analytics software.

#### Link

This website contains hyperlinks to other websites. CodesWholesale.com is not responsible for the privacy policies of these websites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected on this web site. We can make no promises or guarantees regarding data collection on the hyperlinked pages and sites that are not owned by CodesWholesale.com. We therefore recommend that you read the privacy policy/ statement for each site you visit.

#### Communication

At time, we may send out email messages alerting you about products' availability, reminding about providing feedback or for promotional offers. In addition, you will hear from us in case of any administrative purposes, or if you contact us with regard to any particular reason e.g. receiving your orders. Sign up for our newsletter if you wish to receive promotional materials from CodesWholesale.com. Administrative e-mails will not contain any of them.

#### Security

CodesWholesale.com takes reasonable measures to protect your personal information. When you submit any personal information via our website, it is protected from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure both on- and off-line. Your personal information is not shared outside the company without your permission, except under the conditions explained above. CodesWholesale.com does not rent or sell personal information to third parties.

#### Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

Should your personal information have changed, or you no longer wish to receive e-mails from CodesWholesale.com, you can correct, update, delete or deactivate your personal information by contacting us.

#### Notification of Changes

Once we decide to change our privacy policy, any alterations to this privacy statement will be posted here.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about the privacy policy or security at our web site, you can contact us via the form at the bottom of this page.
